/*
The contents of the JSON data file, added to a JavaScript variable, so that it can be parsed by the main JS script.
A work-around for the problem of importing the data using HttpRequest.
*/

var myData = '[{"question":"Which of these is not a concept associated with databases?","possibleAnswers":["View","Table","Index","Desk"],"rightAnswer":"Desk"},{"question":"Which of these is another way of saying a decimal numbering system?","possibleAnswers":["Base99","Base7","Base10","Base4"],"rightAnswer":"Base10"},{"question":"What is an error condition that occurs during the execution of a Java program?","possibleAnswers":["Discretion","Calumniation","Dissolution","Exception"],"rightAnswer":"Exception"},{"question":"As opposed to a variable, the value of which construct in a programming language never changes?","possibleAnswers":["Fixed","Stuck","Static","Constant"],"rightAnswer":"Constant"},{"question":"What does the acronym (pixel) refer to?","possibleAnswers":["Photo element","Picture information","Picture element","Phosphor location"],"rightAnswer":"Picture element"},{"question":"Which programming language was created by James Gosling?","possibleAnswers":["awk","JavaScript","Java","C"],"rightAnswer":"Java"},{"question":"A (Universal Machine) was a concept designed by which computer scientist?","possibleAnswers":["Alan Turing","Claude Shannon","John von Neumann","Charles Babbage"],"rightAnswer":"Alan Turing"},{"question":"Which language was once known as Oak, and then Green?","possibleAnswers":["Java","Pascal","C#","JavaScript"],"rightAnswer":"Java"},{"question":"Which of these terms indicates that the OS does not have a requested (page)?","possibleAnswers":["Page crash","Interrupt","Stack overflow","Page fault"],"rightAnswer":"Page fault"},{"question":"In JavaScript, how many times is a (do while) loop guaranteed to loop?","possibleAnswers":["1","Infinitely until stopped","Variable","0"],"rightAnswer":"1"},{"question":"In JavaScript, which choice is the 5th element of the array named: score?","possibleAnswers":["*score[5]","#score[4]","score[4]","score[5]"],"rightAnswer":"score[4]"},{"question":"A (query plan) is associated with which of these areas of computer science?","possibleAnswers":["Assemblers","Compilers","Interpreters","Databases"],"rightAnswer":"Databases"},{"question":"Which of these is a valid IP4 address format?","possibleAnswers":["10.10.255.0","all of them","192.168.1.1","0.0.0.0"],"rightAnswer":"all of them"},{"question":"Files with .pl extension are associated with programming language?","possibleAnswers":["Ruby","Python","Perl","PHP"],"rightAnswer":"Perl"},{"question":"Which of these programs is one of the first to be executed when a computer starts?","possibleAnswers":["Memory Manager","Bootloader","Device Driver","Task Scheduler"],"rightAnswer":"Bootloader"},{"question":"Which company collaborated with Microsoft to build OS/2?","possibleAnswers":["IBM","HP","Xerox","Apple"],"rightAnswer":"IBM"},{"question":"Which is a method of interprocess communication under Microsoft Windows?","possibleAnswers":["MS-RPC","Inter-Thread Transport","Dynamic Data Exchange","MS-Arhicom"],"rightAnswer":"Dynamic Data Exchange"},{"question":"What does an SSL certificate do?","possibleAnswers":["Tells websites about you","Blocks spam from webpages","Tracks your web surfing","Validates website authenticity"],"rightAnswer":"Validates website authenticity"},{"question":"Which of the following are VPN tunneling protocols?","possibleAnswers":["L2TP","PPTP","IPsec","All of these"],"rightAnswer":"All of these"},{"question":"Which of these is a famous text editor?","possibleAnswers":["Vim","Grep","Find","Pipe"],"rightAnswer":"Vim"},{"question":"What does the (RS) in RS-232 stand for?","possibleAnswers":["Recommended Standard","Request to Send","Request Standard","Ready to Send"],"rightAnswer":"Recommended Standard"},{"question":"Which intermediate form are Java programs compiled to?","possibleAnswers":["C","Macros","Machine Language","Bytecode"],"rightAnswer":"Bytecode"},{"question":"Which of these is NOT a type of algorithm?","possibleAnswers":["Parallel","Randomized","Distributed","Straightforward"],"rightAnswer":"Straightforward"},{"question":"A segment in an IPv6 addresses can be any any hexadecimal value from 0 to?","possibleAnswers":["1000","FFFF","1024","8092"],"rightAnswer":"FFFF"},{"question":"which of these concepts in databases did Edgar Codd invent?","possibleAnswers":["NoSQL","Indexing","Relational Model","Concurrency"],"rightAnswer":"Relational Model"}]';